University of Connecticut, Office of Public Information (OPI) Records 1979.0011
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series VII: Morgue Files, 1963-1984
  - 1974-1984
    - Dean's List, 1976
    - Dean's List, 1977
    - Dean's List, 1978, Spring
    - Dean's List, 1979 (Box 22)
    - Dean's List, 1979, Spring
    - Dean's List, 1980
    - Dean's List, 1980, Spring
    - Dean's List, 1981
    - Dean's List, 1982
    - Dean's List, 1982, Fall
    - Dean's List, 1982, Spring
    - Dean's List, 1983
    - Dean's List, 1983, Fall
    - Dean's List, 1984
    - Senate (Box 23)
    - Senate
    - University Senate, 1984-1985
    - Capital Press Room reporters, list of
    - New England Society of Newspaper Editors
    - Student Welfare Committee
    - Division of Housing and Food Services
    - Student Union (Box 23)
    - Technical Service Center
    - The 3 R's
    - SB 842 - tuition, 1981
    - University Senate, 1974-1976
    - University of Connecticut Foundation
    - University Patents, Inc.
    - Radio-TV-General
    - Publications Department
    - Faculty tenure
    - Urban Semester
    - Urban Academy
    - Urban Semester
    - Urban Studies, Institute of
    - Vandalism
    - Veterinary School Proposal
    - Video III, 1981
    - Water Resources, Institute of
    - Year End Round Up
- Series VIII: Unviersity Presidents, undated, 1935-1973
  - Albert Jorgensen (Box 24)
    - Biography, (2 folders)
    - Commencement Address
    - Convocation: 25th Anniversary
    - Correspondence, (2 folders)
    - News releases, (2 folders)
    - Presidency, 1935-1946
    - Presidency, 1956-1957
    - Welcome messages
  - Homer Babbidge
    - Advisory Committee on Physically Handicapped
    - Annual report
    - Babbidge, Homer, (6 folders)
    - Babbidge, Homer, 1962-1963
    - Babbidge, Homer, 1973
    - Biography
    - Commission on University Governance (Box 25)
    - Committee on Long-Range Growth
    - Easter Egg hunt
    - Lecture series
    - Letters, 1963
    - Long-Range Finance Planning Committee
    - Newsclips
    - Presidential Search Advisory Committee
    - Press tours
    - Releases
    - Retirement, (2 folders)
    - Speeches, 1962-1963; (2 folders)
    - Speeches, 1964-1966; (2 folders)
    - Speeches, 1967-1969
    - Speeches, 1970-1972
    - UConn Under Babbidge
    - United Nations Day
    - Views on UConn
    - Weekly calendar
  - Glenn Ferguson
    - Ferguson, Glenn W., (4 folders)
    - Ferguson, Patricia
    - Newsclip File
    - Newsclips (Box 26)
    - Resignation
    - Speeches